[
    {
        "question": "All Egyptians ............ Salah for his skill and generosity.",
        "choices": [
            "inquire",
            "admire",
            "derive",
            "role play"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "admire"
    },
    {
        "question": "The Egyptian ............ in London welcomed and supported the Egyptian handball team.",
        "choices": [
            "Frequency",
            "stadium",
            "Maasai",
            "community"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "community"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is correct?",
        "choices": [
            "A society",
            "A community",
            "A society",
            "A community"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "A society"
    },
    {
        "question": "We all know that water ............ has become a must.",
        "choices": [
            "wasting",
            "donating",
            "conservation",
            "support"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "conservation"
    },
    {
        "question": "Although he is rich, he works hard to ............ his desire for success.",
        "choices": [
            "satisfy",
            "donate",
            "conserve",
            "monitor"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "satisfy"
    },
    {
        "question": "When we do not know who paid the money, we say it is a ........... . donation.",
        "choices": [
            "antonym",
            "synonym",
            "synonymous",
            "anonymous"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "anonymous"
    },
    {
        "question": "All fans cheered Ip when the players ............ the field .",
        "choices": [
            "ploughed",
            "took",
            "lost",
            "missed"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "took"
    },
    {
        "question": "The livestock on this farm ............ looked after by three workers.",
        "choices": [
            "is",
            "are",
            "is or are",
            "has"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "is or are"
    },
    {
        "question": "The cattle on this farm ............ looked after by three workers.",
        "choices": [
            "is",
            "are",
            "is or are",
            "has"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "are"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the ............ , eating too much food causes overweight.",
        "choices": [
            "long term",
            "field",
            "hometown",
            "desire"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "long term"
    }
]